http://www.thehistorymakers.com/privacy-policy

*
Enter your The HistoryMakers username.
Password
*
Enter the password that accompanies your username.
Explore The HistoryMakers Archives
Become a member today!
Privacy Policy
This notice applies to all information collected or submitted on www.thehistorymakers.org. We collect transactions, including searches, video plays, your volunteered comments, and search filter actions. The transactions are marked with an anonymized tag (a series of numbers and letters) that uniquely identifies you, but which by itself is meaningless. Your email address and personally identifiable information are stored only once, during registration, and stored separately and securely to better protect your privacy.
The information we collect
Your search and other transaction information is used in research reports only in anonymized form. The data is used by researchers to improve the interface to www.thehistorymakers.org, and by The HistoryMakers to add to its database and provide a way of us contacting you to make you a part of our ongoing user base. The data is used for auditing, research and analysis in order to maintain, protect and improve our services, for ensuring the technical functioning of our network, and for developing new services. Your contact information will be used only by The HistoryMakers to contact you. It will be used for critical information regarding the development of The HistoryMakers archives. Your address is not used for any other purpose, and is not shared with outside parties. We use non-identifying and aggregate information to better design our website and perhaps in the future to share with advertisers. For example, we may tell an advertiser that X number of individuals visited a certain area on our website, or that Y number of men and Z number of women filled out our registration form, but we would not disclose anything that could be used to identify those individuals. Finally, we never use or share the personally identifiable information provided to us online in ways unrelated to the ones described above without also providing you an opportunity to opt-out or otherwise prohibit such unrelated uses.
The way we use information
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
Our commitment to data security
To prevent unauthorized access, maintain data accuracy, and ensure the correct use of information, we have put in place appropriate physical, electronic, and managerial procedures to safeguard and secure the information we collect online.
How you can access or correct your information
Your personally identifiable information is collected only once, during registration. We allow for a password change through the link on the sign-in screen. We do not at this time have a mechanism in place to correct errors in your personally identifiable information. You can send email to the contact address below to retire an account, and then can register to set up a new account.
How to contact us
Should you have other questions or concerns about these privacy policies, please send us an email to the following contact address: info@thehistorymakers.org.
Back to top
